Next time preview
The first question is: In one word, how would you describe Meiyan?
Yes, I do.
Mona Min
She is a breather, but a reliable big sister to everyone.
She cries easily when she has a hard time.
She usually takes the lead in organizing the dance and MC sessions.
She's always there to help us out with her leadership and behind the scenes work.
Thank you very much.
That's great. It's not a hassle.
I'm glad you like her so much.
Yeah, a big fan.
I'll have to get something for Monamin.
In the comments section.
What are you doing?
I don't often get things in the comments section.
No, you don't.
Nagamachi.
Oh, hello, Harold.
I'm negative, but I actually have a strong side.
People around me have the impression that I'm a crier.
It's true that I often see you crying.
But in front of the members, I think she tries to be a big sister
I think she tries to be a big sister in front of the members.
Oh, I see.
That's right.
She's trying to be a big sister.
Okay, next, next.
Fu-chan Saki
After you've been behind the scenes, after you've been shaken in, make sure you check the video.He's a behind-the-scenes guy, and after the shake-in, he'll check the video carefully and let everyone know what needs to be fixed.
and tell everyone what needs to be fixed.
I'm glad.
You know what I mean?
I know, I know, I know.
I'm glad.
I know.
Yuyi-yui Takanashi
It's unique.
I was just thinking about doing that.
It's okay, though. Not at all.
Actually, I have the strongest mentality
Although there are times when I'm weak
But you've been able to fight in this world for almost 10 years.
I've noticed that you have a very strong mentality when I entered the entertainment business.
I think one of the reasons for your mental strength is that you have a strong core in a good way
I have a lot of respect for you.
Wow, that makes me happy.
Thank you.
That's great. What a great, easy-to-understand writing.
That's what I'd expect from a publicist.
It's all neatly organized.
It's full of information.
You explain everything.
Thank you very much.
Next.
In a survey called Meinawa that only I know about.
I'm a little scared.
Let's start with you, Ms. Sasaki.
Ah, Fuuna SasakiAh, Fuuna Sasaki
Fuuna Sasaki
I forgot the spectacular view at the rehearsal for my one-man show.
I was really worried about it at that time.
But the other day, when I saw the rehearsal scene again on Youtube
When I saw the rehearsal scene again on youtube
I saw myself without "Zekkei" on the screen.
I wanted to give a sigh of relief that I still cared.
I'm soooo sorry, I don't know, I'm forever sorry.
Right?
Yes, I already knew I needed it for the one-man show.
I knew I was going to make a "making of" kind of a film.
I left it by the front door, but I left it there.
I already called you on the train on the way there.
Yeah, to Mikuni.
I was the first one to call you.
What should I do? I'm sure he'll use it.
Yeah, he's going to check it so hard.
Of course I'm going to use it.
But you'll remember me when you see me not wearing it.
And then he'd say, "Oh, I'm sure I'll use it.
I'm sure I'll look bad, but...
But everyone said, "It's okay, it's okay.
I kept thinking we were all going to commit seppuku.
He apologized first.
He apologized so much.
That's great.
During rehearsal.
Yes, I don't wear a dress in the scenery every day.
Thank you very much.
He said something like, "I'm sorry.You said something like I'm sorry.
It was embarrassing and I will forever say I'm sorry.
Ryo kana tsume
Every time before a live performance or a photo shoot
I face the mirror and feel dissatisfied
I tell them that I'm always perfect, but they don't believe me.
What?
I mean, I look in the mirror before every gig.
I don't know what's missing.
You know what I mean?
I know, Mikun.
I feel like I say that a lot.
It's always something different.
But I don't know what's missing.
I'm doing everything.
Yeah, it's not always the same.
What's different? What's different? I'm sure I ask a lot.
But they all tell me I'm cute and that it's okay.
They're all so kind.
I feel like I'm lying. I'm lying.
I'm not lying.
You know, Miku...
I doubt it
They call him Mobaba, Mobajou
Using the same moba as me
Something like...
I don't know... something... I've been calling him Mobajou for a while.
You know, the, the high school group.
They were saying "Mobaba, Mobaba, Mobaba!
What do you mean, "Mobaba"? I was like, "What's Mobaba?What is Mobaba? I was like, "What is Mobaba?
And then he said he felt like he had a genegear.
Mobaba?
Oh, you're in high school too.
No, it's Mobajou.
But you called it "Dokodemo Charger" at first?
Dokodemo Charger?
I've been calling you "Dokodemo Charger" for a long time.
I'd get made fun of.
I thought, "Oh, this is different...
So I switched to Mobaba.
And then Miri made fun of me.
I said "moba-joo".
So when Miri made fun of me.
I started saying Mobaba.
No, not "Mobaba.
Then, can I call you Mobajou?
No, just "moba-joo".
Mobajou then
Sorry, Miri.
What's Mobaba?
You look like an old lady.
Right?
But you know, I don't really understand JK.
I mean, you're a JK too, but...
I don't understand JK.
I don't get it.
Okay, up the tempo!
Let's pick up the tempo!
Takanashi.
I'm very close with my mom.I'm very close with my mom.
But we fight sometimes.
The more they fight, the better they get along. That's a perfect description.
Are you okay? Mom.
Mom, are you okay with this?
No, it's fine. It's fine.
We fight a lot, that's for sure.
And then I show Yui the line.
I'll tell Yui that we had a fight.
But then we usually go out to eat.
"We'll make up soon," or "We'll forget about it when we get out of the bathtub.
Or she'll forget about it when she gets out of the bathtub.
That's how it is.
I know it's not much, but...
But I always tell Yui
I tell Yui that we had a fight again.
Saito
You were cute for a while. I always said you were cute.
Stop it, really
Those days are over.
Lately I've been saying "Mikkun kawachii".
He's the type to become pro-rexy afterwards
I'm sorry, I'm a little...
I used to be the type to say "cute" and "pretty" a lot when I was in high school.
I used to say "kawachi" and "oi" a lot when I was in high school.
I used to call you Haru-chan.
I'm going to wish I hadn't done that when I was a college student.
Advice
I've seen it from afar and thought about it.
But because it's spring, it's forgivable.
I wasn't so bad myself.I'm not so sure about me.
Thank you very much.
Okay, is there anything you want me to fix?
I'd love to hear.
I think there's a lot.
I get the shakes, you know?
I thought I was gonna shake.
Would you like me to do it?
Yes, please.
Nagamatsu.
I know I can be negative at times.
But to me, you're the cutest, coolest, funniest, best storyteller, and I adore you!
So please be more confident.
I'm so happy for you.
You're saying that in a very full course!
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
Well then, let's go a little longer.
Natsume.
Lack of confidence.
But I think it's that kind of modesty that makes everyone love me.
I don't have anything to fix.
Aaah...
Suddenly I'm a college student.
I don't have it.
No, no, no, no, no, thank you very much.
Hayashi
Hayashi.
I don't have it
Four letters.
That's kinda cool.That's kinda cool.
I'm sure you've done a survey of everyone so far, and I'm sure you've written something you'd like to see fixed.
You've written about 3 or 2 of them.
You wrote about 2 out of 3.
And yet...
I feel a little guilty if everyone says they don't have it.
So from now on, you'll write, "No, I don't have it.
She says she doesn't have any.
That's cool.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Takanashi.
Maruichi
Yui's a good friend.
Yeah...
Ajitama harassment
When we go out for ramen together, he strongly encourages me to eat ajitama in one bite.
I'm a little scared that if I eat ajitama in one bite, it might get stuck in my throat
That's true.
But you know what, Yui, you don't hit me.
That's right.
When the three of us went there together...
Of course it's good to split one ajitama in half like this, but...
But when you go with just one, you get the texture, the flavor, your delivery...
You can feel the texture, the flavor, and your delivery in your mouth.
That's why I've been asking you to do it.
I've been spreading the word that I want you to do it, but you won't do it because you don't want to hit me.
So you're doing it again.
Yes, I always go with Yui, but...
But he won't listen to me.
He doesn't listen to me.They don't listen to me.
Harassment.
That's what I'm talking about.
It was harassment.
I'm sorry.
Maruni.
She doesn't want to come with us.
Meina loves ramen, but she refuses to go with us, except for the spicy ramen.
Sad. I want to go with her.
Well, I've taken her to a lot of ramen restaurants.
You're right, I have to go out with her.
You don't want to go out with her, do you?
Next turn.
I don't want to.
You're coming.
Oh, my God.
I'll go if you're coming.
I don't get it.
You have to be there for the photo shoot.
He's a private person.
He can't go unless the camera's rolling.
That's great.
I can't go.
I can't go unless the camera's rolling.
Not at the office.
I'll see you there.
We're all in the same office.
Please, I don't want to go, Yui.
Saito I often take a selfie with someone's phone without permission.
It's true, people tend to do it.Yes, we tend to do that.
You're prone to it.
I'm sorry.
Saito 2nd
I always stay up unbelievably late, and I'm worried about my body, so I go to bed early.
I'll do my best.
Okay.
I want to say something.
Natsume, I want to go to Disney and eat ramen with you.
Let's go.
Ramen's fine, but Disney's not so good.
I'm just saying...
It's easier to go alone than with everyone else.
It's a bit of a circle.
But if you switch it up and go with friends, people will be fine.
Will you come tomorrow or not?
Let's plan ahead and go with Ruff Ruff.
Ruff ruff.
Yoshimura, you always say you lack confidence, but there are many moments when I think you're really on a completely different level, in your work ethic, in your performance, in your gestures.
I'm glad you guys feel the same way.
It's true.
It's totally true.
Really? I'm a little skeptical.
Like you're up to something, like you want something.
No, I don't.
Well, that's what I thought for a minute, but it's okay to take it as a compliment.
Thank you.
Take good care of it.
I'll build up my confidence.I'll gain confidence.
TakanashiLately in the past week, I've had a number of train delays, missed the last train, had bird droppings fall on my head, and just generally haven't had any luck.
I'm not lucky.
Ramen restaurants where people with bad luck go to eat
There is a ramen shop called Hyori in Baba, Takada.
It's a ramen shop called Hyori in Bubba's Takada, and it's also because it's Yuichi's ramen shop.
There is a ramen restaurant called "Hyori" in Takada Bhaba, where people who are not so lucky go to eat ramen.
There is a kind of spicy miso ramen.
It has a big portion of fried bean curd on top of the ramen.
and garlic with a dash of Se-oil.
And bean sprouts and vegetables are also on top.
It's a very hearty ramen.
It's spicy, so it's perfect for Yuichan.
and because of the volume difference, even if you're having a bad day
I think it will give you more energy and make you work harder.
I'm sure she'll be able to do her best.
That's why I'm going to choose Hyori.
It's been a long time since I've been here.
I haven't been here for a long time, either.
I'm worried.
It's a little awkward coming in here so suddenly, but...
I hope I did okay.
I thought it was totally fine.
You should try it.
Please go.
Yes, Saito.
When I see Hibi, it reminds me of Hibi's Meina-chan.
Cute!
Cute.
Because it's cute.Because...
Of course you're happy.
Thank you.
You're so cute.
The last one is Miku's.
What?
It's a "miku". It's a "miku".
Let's hear it. Let's hear it.
Thank you for everything.
And for the dancing.
I'm glad you're taking everything so seriously.
Let's go eat blue ramen!
I, Mika Fujisaki, am always the centerpiece.
Oh, I'm so happy.
Thank you.
I forgot to tell you myself.
I wrote it down in so much detail, it's embarrassing.
It's true, the ramen noodles are blue.
Because the noodles are blue.
There's a famous ramen shop in Shibuya called Kiposhi.
Chintan
Oh, it's not "Chintan".
Is it a chicken type ramen?
And it's blue soup.
It's also very tasty!
Let's go.
Ooh!
I really want you to go eat there, so...
I'm going with Mikuni.
Yay.Yay.
So, how was your first visit and talk?
Well, I'm glad it was my first time with you.
I really don't know...
I'm good friends with all the members, but...
I'm not really good at communicating on LINE or SNS.
I'm not really good at communicating with people on social networking sites.
I don't really use LINE.
But Mikun is very active in sending me messages.
We talk a lot and have a lot in common.
It was refreshing to receive compliments from a member I talk to a lot.
It was also refreshing to receive compliments directly from him.
I'm glad it was Mikun who was on the other end of the line.
Thank you very much, everyone.
I'm really happy.
I'm going to work hard for the rest of the recording.
I'm sure you will.
I can do it.
Okay.
So, this is a relay format.
Are there any members you would like to interview?
Monami.
Monamy.
Yes, Monami, since you've given me so many compliments.
Yes, as a gift, I'd like to make another appearance.
Something to eat, maybe with snacks or something.
While you're holding it.
I was thinking of having a rumble contest.
Okay, see you next time.Okay, next time.
Menya and Monamin will have a sshot talk.
Please look forward to it!
That's all for the members' relay talk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you all!
Thank you for watching until the end.
Today we have a pissed off version!
Hey, what's going on with the channel subscriptions?
I can't get enough subscribers!
It's not cool if it doesn't go up!
I know I look like I care about it a lot.
If you've already done it, thank you.
If you haven't, what's wrong with you?
I'm gonna pull your nuts out and make them rattle a lot.
Okay, I'm gonna do the last one.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you.